mykachingkaching.com 2010-11-26

# KaChing KaChing

## Privacy Policy

At KACHING KACHING, we are committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring the security of the information you submit to us. We want your use of the KACHING KACHING web site, and the services we offer, to be productive and safe and we have taken great efforts to keep your information confidential and secure at all times within our system. KACHING KACHING's Privacy Policy illustrates our commitment to your privacy and security. KACHING KACHING does not engage in the selling of personal information, including profile, contact, web usage habits, behavior, buying patterns, or demographic information of our customers, partners or users. We use the information we collect about you to process orders, pay commissions and provide the best and most personalized service possible. We may revise this Privacy Policy occasionally, so please check it frequently.

### The information we collect:

**Registering as an Independent Store Owner:**  
To access all of the functionality of KACHING KACHING as an Independent Store Owner, we require that you have an active store license. You need to become a registered user and agree to comply with the policies laid out in our Terms, Conditions, Policies and Procedures. You must choose a unique username and password to register as a KACHING KACHING Store Owner and to access your account. We also require that you provide your full and legal name, current address, and Social Security Number. A valid email address is necessary so that we may contact you as needed concerning activity that is relevant to your account.

**How We Use Your Information:**  
We may use your email address, mailing address and/or phone number to provide quality customer support or to reach you regarding order status, product or fulfillment issues and other customer service related activities. We may use your email address, mailing address and/or phone number to contact you regarding new product offerings and other aspects of your use of the KACHING KACHING web site.

**Tracking Information**  
Like most every web site, the KACHING KACHING web site records certain tracking information any time someone visits the site. For every web page that is viewed, our web server records an IP address, the operating system, browser version and the name of the page that was viewed. This information is not linked to any specific user and is used in the aggregate to maintain, track performance and improve the KACHING KACHING web service.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small piece of information that is stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. KACHING KACHING uses cookies for the sole purpose of uniquely identifying our users and securing their personal information. We also use cookies to track your order process without requiring reentry or re-verification of contact or password information on each page of the site. Rather than storing this information on KACHING KACHING's server, the cookie is stored in your computer and is activated only when you visit the KACHING KACHING site. Your privacy and security are not compromised when you accept a cookie from the KACHING KACHING web site. No one can access the information except KACHING KACHING.

**Email & "Opt Out" Policy**  
We may use your email address provided during the User Registration process and in the Admin Section to contact you regarding the following: 

  1. Independent Store Owner Registration Status (including confirmation of account signup), 
  2. Order Status, 
  3. Major changes to the website, addition of new products or services, 
  4. Promotional and marketing materials that we think you may find useful.

If you wish to not receive any of these emails you may opt-out by submitting your address to support@kachingkaching.com.

**KACHING KACHING  Website Security**  
The KACHING KACHING web site uses secure sockets layer (SSL) to encrypt the transfer of sensitive information, such as your account password and billing information, from your web browser to our web server. Only the last four (4) digits of your credit card number will be displayed in your account. Emails you send to us may not be secure unless otherwise told that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For this reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as credit card numbers through emails.

**Your Consent:**  
In addition to the circumstances described above, KACHING KACHING may disclose or release information when we, in good faith, believe that doing so is reasonably necessary: (i) to comply with the law; (ii) to enforce or apply the terms of User Agreement; or (iii) to protect the rights, property or safety of kachingkaching.com, our users, or others. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by KACHING KACHING as described in this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our policy, we will post those changes here so you will always know what information we gather, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If you have any questions regarding KACHING KACHING's privacy policy and practices, please direct them to the KACHING KACHING Support Team at [support@kachingkaching.com]().
